# Benjamin Boswick

Master of Landscape Architecture Candidate - M3 Student

A hard-working individual who effectively prioritizes tasks, operating in both independent and group settings. With intense dedication towards academics, a consistent work ethic is displayed. Keeping an open mind is necessary for creativity and retaining new information and experiences in the field.

<b>Contact Information</b>
----------------------------

## Education

Email

ben.boswick@gmail.com

Website

https://boswick.design

<sup>2021/09 -</sup> M.L.Arch., University of Manitoba Present

2018/09 -B. Env.D., University of Manitoba 2021/05

<sup>2016/09</sup> University 1/Faculty of Science, University of Manitoba 2018/05

### Hard Skills

Microsoft Office

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

**AutoCAD** 

Rhino3D

**TwinMotion** 

SketchUp

Adobe Illustrator

VectorWorks

Soft Skills

Communication

Interpersonal Skills

Time Management

Collaboration

Estimation

Dedication

Experience

2021/05 -Sales Associate Present

McMunn and Yates Building Supplies (600 Pembina Highway)

2017/05 - Created and managed sales orders through a Point of Sales system 2019/11

• Developed quotes for various products and structural packages

2015/02 - Direct customer service 2016/10

Tactful handling of challenging situations

• Attained knowledge of an array of products in every department

Assembled merchandising displays

Operated and maintained necessary machinery

Provided ancillary services outside and off-site

# **Associations**

#### 2020-22 Student Mentor and Ambassador

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

· Providing advice and guidance to peers

• Participating as a faculty representative in various events

#### 2020-21 Student Mentorship Program Cofounder

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

Coordinating student mentoring groups

• Ensuring success of participating mentors and mentees

### 2020-21 **Graduation Committee Treasurer**

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Student Architecture Society

Managing committee finances

Communicating and maintaining faculty wear inventory

#### 2019-22 Student Affiliate

Manitoba Association of Landscape Architects (MALA)

Problem Solving

### **Publications** Merchandising

2020-21 "Hidden Communities", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 30 (Individual Project)

2020-21 "Choice-Less", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 30 (Individual Project)

2019-20 "Urban Orchard", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 29 (Individual Project)

2018-19 "Untitled", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 28 (Collaborative Project)